>> Yeah, so we also have settings over here.
If I click settings, you'll see that we're headed to the settings of this chatbot.
I can change my name.
I can download the chat history.
I can delete account.
I can go to voice settings and change the Py Voice,
my preferred voice over here.
>> Hi, it's lovely to meet you.
My name is Py and I'm your personal AI.
>> How does this voice sound?
>> I can also go to share Py with others.
Yeah, it's nothing special.
We have help and feedback, privacy policy, nothing more.
It's just about the name, about the history, deleting account.
As you see, it doesn't even have a dark mode as I'm aware and as I'm seeing,
it's just a light mode and by clicking new chat,
we can always come back and start talking about something new, right?